M. Dheo Fuady

Cibubur, Indonesia | P: +62 82134457957 | fuadydheo@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/m-dheo-fuady-16884813a/

SUMMARY

A caring and dedicated teacher with 4 years of experience teaching on vocational high school and devising scaffolded lesson plans working within the national curriculum, including creating curriculum for developing student skill for industry. As Edutech Program Manageí with holistic knowledge of developing curriculum and planning píogíam to develop engagement and awaíeness.

EXPERIENCE

Operation Manager - Eudeka

May 2023 – now

- Strategic Planning: Develop and implement operational strategies aligned with the organization's goals and objectives.
- Community Platform Enhancement: Strategically enhance the programmer community, transitioning from its current size of 20 members to a robust network of 1000 members only in 1 month.
- Performance Monitoring: Monitor key performance indicators (KPIs) to track the performance of various departments and processes.
- Problem Solving: Identify operational challenges and bottlenecks, and implement effective solutions to address them.
- Quality Control: Implement quality control measures to maintain high standards of products or services.

Program Manager and Tutor – Walnut Coding

November 2022 - May 2023

- Teaching basic programming concepts with implementation pedagogy and designing engaging learning programs for students.
- Create informative content about technology and gaming to improve participants technology literacy : *link*
- Make localize reports with bahasa and more simple for Indonesian parents and students but full information how progress that student : link
- Achieve stabilize renewal rate up to 50% to improve learning consistency of participants until Q3
- Localize curriculum to make easier implement in Indonesia : link
- Create education schedule and calendar for participants
- Create forecast renewal strategy from for all student information

Frontend Facilitator Part Time – Binar Academy

July 2021 – May 2023

- Guidance students follow a learning path and share knowledge all about front-end development to students.
- Guidance mini project and final project and implement andragogy technique during class.

• Create quizzes and worksheets for students to work on during practicum.

Program Manager (Project Based) - Apiary Academy

Agustus 2022 – November 2022

- Create a product manager curriculum suitable for students with documentation and measurability.
- Successfully helped the apiary academy qualify for the Kampus Merdeka Batch 4.

Tutor Coding for Kids Part Time- HacktivKidz

January 2022 – June 2022

• Sharing knowledge about programming using roblox studio, a thunkable platform that implements pedagogy techniques.

Vice Principal of Curriculum Affairs – IDN Boarding School

June 2021 – July 2022

- Make a strong curriculum administration and make efficient operational teaching methods: link.___
- Make a good documentation curriculum and progress report to maintain progress student learning: link.

Mentor Bangkit Academy (Part Time) - Bangkit Academy

May 2021 – June 2022

- As a mentor, I have the responsibility to maintain a mentee for every progress capstone based on bangkit curriculum.
- Consultative role is valuable for mentees to define their problem and implement their ideas into a go-to- market product and implement andragogy technique during class.

Academic Program Coordinator (Studi Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak)

January 2021 - June 2022

- Create a tech curriculum that is suitable for the tech industry.
- Increase 50% graduate absorb in industry and Develop robust modules and increase fundamental skills of students and make students know about terminology in tech industry area.

Teacher Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak - IDN Boarding School

Augustus 2020 – January 2021

- Teaching and sharing knowledge to student around website development
- Teaching framework Node.js, React.Js, implement pedagogy technique.
- Exercise logical thinking students through pseudocode and flowchart
- Teaching fundamental javascript, implement pedagogy technique

EDUCATION

STIKOM CKI - Information Technology

SKILLS

Curriculum Development Advance Product Management Advance Coding Teaching Skill Advance Project Management Advance React.JS Intermediate Javascript Intermediate Block Based Programming Advance Phyton Intermediate Data Analyst Intermediate

LANGUAGE

English : Fluent